{
    "subject": "resource/Crooked_I",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Hip_hop_music",
    "human_readable": "Crooked I's genre is Hip hop music.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9736937284469604,
            "question": "Is Crooked I a hip hop artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9058005213737488,
            "question": "Crooked I is a musician in which genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8316771984100342,
            "question": "What genre of music is Crooked I known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7624121904373169,
            "question": "If you were to describe Crooked I's music, what genre would you use?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7411400675773621,
            "question": "What kind of music does Crooked I make?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7398892045021057,
            "question": "To which musical genre does Crooked I belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.736212968826294,
            "question": "In what style of music does Crooked I primarily perform?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6517813801765442,
            "question": "What is the primary style of music associated with Crooked I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6233178377151489,
            "question": "Crooked I's music falls under which musical category?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5820127725601196,
            "question": "What is the musical genre that best defines Crooked I's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Crooked I's genre is Hip hop music.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6091_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Crooked I's music falls under which musical category?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6091_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary style of music associated with Crooked I?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6091_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what style of music does Crooked I primarily perform?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6091_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6091_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6091_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6091_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6091_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6091_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6091_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6091_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6091_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6091_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6091_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several pieces of information that support the statement \"Crooked I's genre is Hip hop music.\" For example, they mention his involvement in Long Beach's hip-hop scene and his collaborations with other prominent hip-hop artists."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}